{
    "quiz": {
        "question": [
            {
                "id": 137,
                "_id": "06-01",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "What is a multistep process that gathers and analyzes information about the community to be used to establish priorities for prevention and inform the selection of mitigation strategies?",
                "refPage": "151",
                "possible0": "Community Relation Data (CRD)",
                "possible1": "Community Resource Plan (CRP)",
                "possible2": "Community Risk Intervention (CRI)",
                "possible3": "Community Risk Assessment (CRA)",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 138,
                "_id": "06-02",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "Population distribution, economics, and educational levels are examples of _____ that the FLSE II needs to thoroughly understand to best serve their jurisdiction.",
                "refPage": "152",
                "possible0": "assessments",
                "possible1": "causal chains",
                "possible2": "reliable data sources",
                "possible3": "community demographics",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 139,
                "_id": "06-03",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "The susceptibility of an individual or group to suffer harm or loss from an event is referred to as:",
                "refPage": "152",
                "possible0": "influence.",
                "possible1": "exposure.",
                "possible2": "vulnerability.",
                "possible3": "confirmation.",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 140,
                "_id": "06-04",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "The FLSE II must examine how incidents are affecting _____ by considering human, social, cultural, economic, political, and environmental factors.",
                "refPage": "152",
                "possible0": "causal chain analysis",
                "possible1": "potential ramifications",
                "possible2": "reactive risk reduction",
                "possible3": "confirmed high-risk populations",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 141,
                "_id": "06-05",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "Causal chain analysis examines the series of actions leading to a risk event to determine logical places for:",
                "refPage": "153",
                "possible0": "inclusion.",
                "possible1": "intervention.",
                "possible2": "partnerships.",
                "possible3": "responsibility.",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 142,
                "_id": "06-06",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "Anyone in a community with an interest in the outcome of planning is referred to as a(an):",
                "refPage": "154",
                "possible0": "owner.",
                "possible1": "manager.",
                "possible2": "volunteer.",
                "possible3": "stakeholder.",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 143,
                "_id": "06-07",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "What is prioritized by studying the frequency of occurrences, rates of rise, morbidity, mortality, and the cost generated by incidents?",
                "refPage": "155",
                "possible0": "Risk",
                "possible1": "Mitigation",
                "possible2": "Consensus",
                "possible3": "Rate of return",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 144,
                "_id": "06-08",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "A well-organized, well-resourced risk-mitigation strategy only reduces:",
                "refPage": "155",
                "possible0": "benchmarks.",
                "possible1": "preventable risks.",
                "possible2": "unintended baselines.",
                "possible3": "attainable levels of reduction.",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 145,
                "_id": "06-09",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "An outcome objective creates a(an) _____ against which risk-reduction strategies may be measured.",
                "refPage": "155",
                "possible0": "direction",
                "possible1": "benchmark",
                "possible2": "intervention",
                "possible3": "problem statement",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 146,
                "_id": "06-10",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "Which of the Five E's interventions of a completed community risk assessment is designed to raise awareness, provide information, and ultimately produce a desired behavior?",
                "refPage": "156",
                "possible0": "Education",
                "possible1": "Engineering",
                "possible2": "Economic incentives",
                "possible3": "Emergency response",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 147,
                "_id": "06-11",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "The most important approach to establishing educational priorities, regardless of the method chosen, is to use a process that bases priorities on:",
                "refPage": "157",
                "possible0": "delivery.",
                "possible1": "evaluation.",
                "possible2": "the stakeholders and partners.",
                "possible3": "the communityâ€™s identified risk.",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 148,
                "_id": "06-12",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "As it is not feasible for an educator to reduce community-wide risks alone, the FLSE can seek _____ vested in meeting the goals and objectives of risk-reduction initiatives.",
                "refPage": "157",
                "possible0": "networks",
                "possible1": "witnesses",
                "possible2": "recognition boards",
                "possible3": "community partners",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 149,
                "_id": "06-13",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "What is the often informal process of meeting others and determining how resources can be shared or exchanged in order to further the goals and objectives of risk reduction programs?",
                "refPage": "158",
                "possible0": "Filtering",
                "possible1": "Approach",
                "possible2": "Education",
                "possible3": "Networking",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 150,
                "_id": "06-14",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "While they may not know the risk topic of a fire and life safety education activity, _____  professionals know how to formulate information for the audience.",
                "refPage": "158",
                "possible0": "formal training",
                "possible1": "human resources",
                "possible2": "community outreach",
                "possible3": "educational association",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 151,
                "_id": "06-15",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "What can inform people, both inside and outside the organization, about risk-reduction activities and keep the efforts on track?",
                "refPage": "158",
                "possible0": "Outreach",
                "possible1": "Credibility",
                "possible2": "Recognition",
                "possible3": "Consistency",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 152,
                "_id": "06-16",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "All organizations in the community that address the targeted fire and life safety issues need to be on the same page by using:",
                "refPage": "159",
                "possible0": "outreach.",
                "possible1": "new ideas.",
                "possible2": "recognition.",
                "possible3": "consistent messages.",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 153,
                "_id": "06-17",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "The ultimate goal of any fire and life safety education program is to reach as much of the targeted community as possible with relevant and up-to-date advice on actions and behaviors through:",
                "refPage": "159",
                "possible0": "outreach.",
                "possible1": "recognition.",
                "possible2": "problem-solving.",
                "possible3": "activity evaluations.",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 154,
                "_id": "06-18",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "FEMA's Whole Community Approach to Emergency Management promotes _____ all parts of the community.",
                "refPage": "159",
                "possible0": "in-kind services with",
                "possible1": "confining and limiting",
                "possible2": "engaging and empowering",
                "possible3": "knowledge and skill base determination for",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 155,
                "_id": "06-19",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "One challenge of _____ is participants must work to maintain the focus of the group by reviewing the statement of purpose or mission statement of the group and making sure that all projects and programs focus on the purpose of the organization.",
                "refPage": "160",
                "possible0": "evaluations",
                "possible1": "partnerships",
                "possible2": "in-kind services",
                "possible3": "educator training",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 156,
                "_id": "06-20",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "While networking may be the starting point in forming a partnership, collaborations establish informal partnerships and _____ create formal partnerships.",
                "refPage": "161",
                "possible0": "coalitions",
                "possible1": "messages",
                "possible2": "workloads",
                "possible3": "stakeholders",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 157,
                "_id": "06-21",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "In seeking partnerships, fire and life safety educators need to look for those persons, groups, and organizations that _____ of the fire and life safety education programs.",
                "refPage": "162",
                "possible0": "create coalitions",
                "possible1": "finance activities",
                "possible2": "create formal collaboration",
                "possible3": "match the goals and mission",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 158,
                "_id": "06-22",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "The five common stages groups go through to reach decisions or accomplish tasks that change over time are:",
                "refPage": "165",
                "possible0": "sizing, roles, norms, cohesiveness, and consensus.",
                "possible1": "engaging, planning, organizing, filtering, and adjourning.",
                "possible2": "attraction, formulation, organization, action, and domination.",
                "possible3": "forming, storming, norming, performing, and transforming (or adjourning).",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 159,
                "_id": "06-23",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "What four activities increase the likelihood of a group achieving its objectives?",
                "refPage": "165",
                "possible0": "Consensus, voting, group dynamics, structure",
                "possible1": "Connecting, categorizing, developing, questioning",
                "possible2": "Recognition, accomplishment, proposals, evaluation",
                "possible3": "Communicate objectives, negotiate, resolve conflict, accountability",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 160,
                "_id": "06-24",
                "chapterId": 6,
                "question": "The FLSE must realize that he or she cannot circumvent the due process of an organization or community because _____ affect(s) every facet of society.",
                "refPage": "166",
                "possible0": "politics",
                "possible1": "rationale",
                "possible2": "project support",
                "possible3": "emotional forces",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            }
        ]
    }
}
